Two Worlds. One Magical Secret.
Secret of the Wings is a animation, family,
fantasy film directed by Peggy Holmes.
Tinkerbell wanders into the forbidden Winter woods and meets Periwinkle.
Together they learn the secret of their wings and try to unite the warm
fairies and the winter fairies to help Pixie Hollow.
Tinker Bell (voice), played by Mae Whitman.
Periwinkle (voice), played by Lucy Hale.
Lord Milori (voice), played by Timothy Dalton.
Dewey / Clank (voice), played by Jeff Bennett.
Silvermist (voice), played by Lucy Liu.
Iridessa (voice), played by Raven-Symoné.
Secret of the Wings (originally titled Tinker Bell and the Mysterious Winter Woods or alternatively Tinker Bell and the Secret of the Wings) is a
2012 American animated fantasy film, and the fourth installment in the Disney Fairies franchise, produced by Disneytoon Studios.
It revolves around Tinker Bell, a fairy character created by J.
Barrie in his 1904 play, Peter Pan, or The Boy Who Wouldn't Grow Up, and featured in subsequent adaptations, especially in Disney's
animated works, and how she ventures to the Winter Woods and meets her twin sister, Periwinkle, who is a frost fairy.
The film was directed by Peggy Holmes and co-directed by Bobs Gannaway.
Starring the voices of Mae Whitman, Lucy Liu, Megan Hilty, Raven-Symoné and Angela Bartys, it also features new cast
members who include Lucy Hale, Matt Lanter, Timothy Dalton and Debby Ryan, while Anjelica Huston narrates.
The film explores themes of cold, winter, fairy tale, fairy, sister.